<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:28:29 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Buffer Overflow</title>
      <link>/featured/bof/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:28:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/featured/bof/</guid>
      <description>Buffer overflow attacks have been a topic of discussion in the cybersecurity world for a long time, but I believe there&amp;rsquo;s always room for another perspective.
In this writeup, I will take a unique approach and walk you through the process of executing a buffer overflow attack using VSCode as my code editor and BurpSuite to generate the initial request in Python.
My goal is to provide a clear and concise explanation of this complex topic, so that even those with limited experience can understand the mechanics behind buffer overflow attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffer Overflow</title>
      <link>/posts/bof/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:28:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bof/</guid>
      <description>Buffer overflow attacks have been a topic of discussion in the cybersecurity world for a long time, but I believe there&amp;rsquo;s always room for another perspective.
In this writeup, I will take a unique approach and walk you through the process of executing a buffer overflow attack using VSCode as my code editor and BurpSuite to generate the initial request in Python.
My goal is to provide a clear and concise explanation of this complex topic, so that even those with limited experience can understand the mechanics behind buffer overflow attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me!</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:48:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Proactive and results-driven IT professional with a passion for problem-solving and a strong track record in modern technology. Proven ability to adapt to changing business needs through extensive research and experience in various areas of IT, including networking, helpdesk operations, server administration, virtualization, application development, training, and security. Led successful IT projects and implemented innovative solutions to improve efficiency and security.
Holds a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Computer Science and currently pursuing a Postgraduate Diploma in Network Security and Management Certificate at the University of Winnipeg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Windows 10 to Active Directory using PowerShell</title>
      <link>/posts/powershell02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 14:50:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/powershell02/</guid>
      <description>*Note : This is part of a series for how I build Windows Enterprise Test environment. *
In this guide, I will walk you through the steps to configure a newly installed Windows 10 machine to join an existing Active Directory domain using PowerShell. The commands for the configuration process will be included in a script and each command will be thoroughly explained to help you understand the process.
By the end of this tutorial, you will have a clear understanding of how to join a Windows 10 machine to an Active Directory domain using PowerShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install and Configure Active Directory using PowerShell</title>
      <link>/posts/powershell01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 14:06:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/powershell01/</guid>
      <description>*Note : This is part of a series for how I build Windows Enterprise Test environment. *
In this installment of the series, we will delve into the process of installing and configuring a Windows Active Directory using PowerShell. The goal is to simplify the installation procedure by compiling a set of PowerShell scripts, enabling the creation of a test environment with ease and convenience whenever an application needs to be tested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passwordless Login through SSH</title>
      <link>/posts/passwdssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 10:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/passwdssh/</guid>
      <description>Passwordless SSH logins offer a secure and efficient way to access remote servers. Unlike traditional authentication methods that rely on passwords, passwordless SSH utilizes cryptographic keys to verify your identity. This eliminates the need to constantly enter your username and password, making it faster and more convenient.
It&amp;rsquo;s widely recognized that passwords are vulnerable to hacking and brute force attacks. By using passwordless SSH, you can significantly enhance the security of your remote connections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Application Server</title>
      <link>/posts/pythonnginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 12:33:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pythonnginx/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I will be providing an overview on how I set up an application server to host my Python data visualization using popular frameworks like Bokeh or Dash. The server is built on Ubuntu and utilizes Nginx as a reverse proxy and Certbot for securing the connection with HTTPS.
Please note that this guide is not exhaustive or highly detailed, as it is intended for internal access and use only.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
